Tiffany Wu

Phone: (408) 430-3731 | Email: tiffanywu404@gmail.com | Sunnyvale, CA |

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-wu-5683812b6

Portfolio: https://tiffanywu.work/

User interface and user experience designer passionate about developing cutting-edge digital products. Certificate in UX/UI Design from University of Berkeley, California. Fine arts and social science background that translate to strengths in aesthetics and research skills.

Technical Skills

Technical: Figma, Google Suite, Adobe Creative Suite, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery **UX/UI Design Tools:** Atomic Design, UI Grids and Composition, Heuristic Evaluation, Typography, Imagery, Color Theory, Interaction Design and Iconography, Storyboarding, Decision Flow Diagrams, User Need Identification, User Experience Interviewing, Persona Creation, Insight Synthesis

Additional: Copywriting, Project Management, Presenting, Social Media Management

Selected Projects

Cuesine App | https://motiff.github.io/CaseStudy2/

The aim of this project was to empower busy individuals to cook more by offering an app that simplifies the process of finding and planning meals.

- Skills Used: User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, Persona Creation,
 Competitor Analysis, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping,
 In-Person and Remote User Testing
- Technologies Used: Figma, Miro, Trello, Google Suite, Slack, Zoom
- Team of three other UI/UX design students

HarmonyHub App | https://motiff.github.io/CaseStudy3/

The aim of this project was to help musicians discover and effectively connect with compatible collaborators by offering a new social networking app.

- Skills Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, Persona Creation, Competitor Analysis, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping, Remote User Testing
- Technologies Used: Figma, Miro, Trello, Google Suite, Slack, Zoom
- Team of two other UI/UX design students

Dream Center Website Redesign | https://motiff.github.io/Module-20/

Dream Center is a Los Angeles-based non-profit organization that provides support to those affected by homelessness, hunger, and the lack of education. The aim of this project was to redesign the Dream Center website with a focus on addressing the pain points of potential nonprofit organization volunteers and donors, namely the need for transparency, easier viewing

of and sign up for events, and a personalized user experience that motivates them to contribute more. The redesign involves improvements to readability and new designs for systems such as an interactive impact report and donation tracker, event calendar, and user dashboard.

- Skills Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, Persona Creation, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping, Remote User Testing
- Technologies Used: Figma, Miro, Trello, Google Suite, Slack, Zoom
- Team of four other UI/UX design students

Work Experience

Amazon Lab 126 06/2022 - 11/2022

Business Service Center Associate

Sunnyvale, CA

Provided front desk support, real time customer service, and shipment management in a corporate environment.

Superior Court of California

12/2022 - 5/2023

Legal Process Clerk

Palo Alto, CA

Provided legal service, performed document management and other duties in a government environment.

Internship Experience

App Development Consultant, Comic Book Library Archive Taiwan

08/2024 - current

Participate in user interface design and frontend development phases of the official app to extend platforms to a new generation of readers through multimedia transformation of legacy comic books.

Volunteer Experience

Coordinator, South Bay Mutual Aid

09/2020 - 12/2020

Coordinated aid requests through use of Airtable to facilitate distribution of supplies among members of the community.

Communications Committee Member, Anakbayan San Jose

02/2019 - 09/2019

- Designed and created images and related contents for publications using Canva.
- Prepared presentations to committee meetings.
- Managed contents for social media posts.
- Analyzed and implemented feedback on the organization's events.

Education

Certificate in UX/UI Design University of California, Berkeley April 2024

Project Management Certificate Google certificate program May 2024 - current (Ongoing)

Adobe Creative Suite for UI/UX Foothill College and De Anza College professional training August 2024

Website Design Foothill College professional training August 2023

User Experience (UI/UX) Design Foothill College June 2023

Bachelor of Arts in Sociology, School of Social Science University of California, Irvine June 2022

Associate of Arts in Sociology for Transfer (AA-T), Cum Laude De Anza College September 2019

Advanced Placement course in Computer Programming Homestead High School June 2018